const DECK = [
{
    nQuestion: "Pergunta 1",
    question : "Oque é tibia 111?",
    answer : "O melhor MMORpg do mundo111!"
},
{
    nQuestion: "Pergunta 2",
    question : "Oque é tibia 222?",
    answer : "O melhor MMORpg do mundo222!"
},
{
    nQuestion: "Pergunta 3",
    question : "Oque é tibia333?",
    answer : "O melhor MMORpg do mundo3333!"
},
{
    nQuestion: "Pergunta 4",
    question : "Oque é tibia?4444",
    answer : "O melhor MMORpg do mundo!4444"
},
{
    nQuestion: "Pergunta 5",
    question : "Oque é tibia?555",
    answer : "O melhor MMORpg do mundo!5555"
},
{
    nQuestion: "Pergunta 6",
    question : "Oque é tibia6666?",
    answer : "O melhor MMORpg do mundo666!"
},
{
    nQuestion: "Pergunta 7",
    question : "Oque é tibia7777?",
    answer : "O melhor MMORpg do mundo!7777"
},
{
    nQuestion: "Pergunta 8",
    question : "Oque é tibia888?",
    answer : "O melhor MMORpg do mundo8888!"
},

];

export default DECK;
